[{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980219907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":15577,"timeElapsed":60771},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980227478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7567,"timeElapsed":68342},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980233630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6147,"timeElapsed":74494},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980247958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":14323,"timeElapsed":88822},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980265796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":17834,"timeElapsed":106660},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980274493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":8692,"timeElapsed":115357},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980279099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4604,"timeElapsed":119962},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980287238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":8136,"timeElapsed":128102},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980297200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":9956,"timeElapsed":138063},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980302507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3877,"timeElapsed":143371},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4360,"timeElapsed":147736},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4565,"timeElapsed":152305},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980317305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":5859,"timeElapsed":158169},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3771,"timeElapsed":161944},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980324650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3566,"timeElapsed":165514},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3096,"timeElapsed":168613},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2713,"timeElapsed":171329},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980333305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2838,"timeElapsed":174169},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3695,"timeElapsed":179373},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2790,"timeElapsed":182166},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3185,"timeElapsed":185356},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980350428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5930,"timeElapsed":191292},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2953,"timeElapsed":194249},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980358766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5376,"timeElapsed":199630},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980361631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2861,"timeElapsed":202495},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980364923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3288,"timeElapsed":205787},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372767,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7839,"timeElapsed":213631},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":13877,"timeElapsed":227513},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980392575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4822,"timeElapsed":233439},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980396094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3514,"timeElapsed":236957},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":10712,"timeElapsed":247674},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":6667,"timeElapsed":254345},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980416285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2801,"timeElapsed":257149},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419201,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":260065},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2752,"timeElapsed":262820},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4048,"timeElapsed":266872},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3617,"timeElapsed":270491},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5955,"timeElapsed":277955},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4405,"timeElapsed":282364},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5089,"timeElapsed":287457},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":14113,"timeElapsed":301574},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3979,"timeElapsed":305557},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":24202,"timeElapsed":329765},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4659,"timeElapsed":334429},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4872,"timeElapsed":339307},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"2","question":"Would you like to be famous? In what way?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2845,"timeElapsed":342156},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":11658,"timeElapsed":355535},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":65096,"timeElapsed":420637},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3821,"timeElapsed":424463},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587862,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4259,"timeElapsed":428725},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980591428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3563,"timeElapsed":432292},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3561,"timeElapsed":435856},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2624,"timeElapsed":438484},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980602301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4679,"timeElapsed":443165},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2450,"timeElapsed":445618},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":12926,"timeElapsed":460109},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5624,"timeElapsed":465736},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3626,"timeElapsed":469366},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4729,"timeElapsed":474100},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5639,"timeElapsed":479745},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3607,"timeElapsed":483355},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4620,"timeElapsed":487980},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":9074,"timeElapsed":497058},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4227,"timeElapsed":501293},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":118824,"timeElapsed":621527},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980799198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":18530,"timeElapsed":640062},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2694,"timeElapsed":642760},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980805438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3537,"timeElapsed":646302},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980807887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2445,"timeElapsed":648751},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980811340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3451,"timeElapsed":652204},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980813760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2416,"timeElapsed":654624},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":5876,"timeElapsed":660503},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":663241},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980826692,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4311,"timeElapsed":667556},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":6146,"timeElapsed":674958},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980837553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3454,"timeElapsed":678417},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3166,"timeElapsed":681587},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2793,"timeElapsed":684385},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2727,"timeElapsed":687117},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2837,"timeElapsed":689957},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2432,"timeElapsed":692392},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980854516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2983,"timeElapsed":695380},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980859718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5199,"timeElapsed":700581},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980868404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":7193,"timeElapsed":709268},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980872247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3841,"timeElapsed":713111},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980877349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5099,"timeElapsed":718213},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980881059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3708,"timeElapsed":721923},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980885379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4316,"timeElapsed":726243},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3507,"timeElapsed":729752},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980892769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3878,"timeElapsed":733633},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3277,"timeElapsed":736912},{"subjectID":"x3q7tnxc3q","prolificID":"67327ff27baf0c0eabc98887","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2210983520328206ed0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6997,"timeElapsed":743911}]